all-generic-meds.com 2018-03-02

# Privacy Policy Online Pharmacy

This Policy applies as between you, the User of this Web Site and All-generic-meds.com the owner and provider of this Web Site. This Policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us in relation to your use of the Web Site and any Services or Systems therein.

All-generic-meds.com is dedicated to providing ease of navigation, affordability and the highest level of security in respect of your online purchase of medications. We understand that your health is of utmost importance and that the details thereof should be kept confidential and held in the strictest of confidence. In saying this we also appreciate the risks that are associated with online purchases. In order to maintain the highest level of security at all times our site makes use of sophisticated 128 bit SSL security to encrypt your data.

Furthermore, at All-generic-meds.com we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and using the best available technology to ensure your security whilst you are on our site. We request you to register on our site prior to using certain areas of the website. You will be asked to enter your personal information including “sensitive personal data” as defined under the Data Protection Act 1998 (“the Act”).

The information you provide including personal identification information will never be released to any third party without your prior written consent. We will not use your information to send you any offers or emails without your prior written consent. All-generic-meds.com does not advocate the use of spam emails to send unnecessary information and will not use your information for this purpose. Your data will only be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act.

By registering on our site and entering the aforementioned “sensitive personal data,” you accept the terms of this privacy agreement and grant us explicit consent to collect and store such data. However, bearing this in mind we warrant that we will limit the collection and use of your private data to the minimum required for delivery of your orders and development and improvement of our services.

All personal information supplied to All-generic-meds.com will be held in utmost security and in accordance with our internal security policy and the parameters of the law. These privacy guidelines are communicated to all our employees to ensure your personal information remains protected and is held under the strictest confidence,

This Privacy Statement and Policy applies only to information collected from you when you visit our site. It does not apply to any information supplied voluntarily by means of direct email or any other means.

You are advised that All-generic-meds.com does contain links to other websites including the sites of our affiliates. As per the terms of our internal security policy we do not share your personal information with these websites. We are also not responsible for their privacy policies. Prior to entering into any transactions on any of these websites, we strongly advise and encourage you to peruse and understand the privacy policies of those companies. This Privacy Statement and Policy applies to All-generic-meds.com only and not to linked and or our affiliate websites.

Notice of changes in the privacy statement will be prominently displayed on the home page whenever such changes are affected. All-generic-meds.com reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Statement at any time. You are advised you to check our Privacy Statement from time to time.

By your continued use of this website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement.
